http://www.whittingtonsjerky.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Special Programs
Any Soldier ProgramFor Our Troops - Sticks for PicsPictures From Our TroopsFrequent Buyer Club
Sign up to our newsletter
Sign up for our monthly Newsletter to recieve Recipes, Stories, & Special Discount Codes!
Home
FAQsPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy. . .Whittington’s Jerky Inc. Customer Internet Privacy Statement for our website, www.whittingtonsjerky.com
Introduction:
Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how Whittington’s Jerky, Inc. collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our site.
I. Information collected online:
Whittington’s Jerky, Inc. collects information required to complete and fulfill your order, including name, billing address, shipping address, phone number, email address and payment information. When you complete any form on our site, your information is written to a secure file.
When you shop our online store, a SESSION ID tracks movements and your IP address is stored for authentication and verification reasons only. This is standard in all shopping cart programs. We use the industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol that encrypts personal information being transferred over the Internet.
Some information is collected as you browse our site for the purpose of analyzing what pages are accessed and to review the top domain addresses that visit our site. No personal information about you or your business is created during this process.
Cookies are used to identify you and your movement through our store. A cookie is a small file stored on your computer, which expires by a certain date, or can be deleted by you.
II. How we use or share the information we collect:
Billing, Shipping, Contact and Payment information are collected by Whittington’s Jerky, Inc. to complete your order request.
Only Whittington’s Jerky employees and delivery personnel will have access to your information and only for stated purposes such as order fulfillment.
Occasionally, Whittington’s Jerky, Inc. will send out special Internet offers via email.
All information collected while using www.whittingtonsjerky.com is for the sole use of Whittington’s Jerky, Inc. and will not be sold or given to outside agencies or persons for marketing purposes.
III. Marketing uses of the collected information.
If you do not wish to receive periodic Whittington’s Jerky, Inc. Internet Special Offers, you may send us an email to jerky@moment.net and request that your email address be removed from our mailing list.
IV. Consumer inquiries about your information or our privacy policy.
If you have concerns or questions regarding how we use your information, or our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by USPS Mail, Phone or Email.
Mail:Whittington’s Jerky Inc.P.O. Box 8JOHNSON CITY, Texas 78636
Phone (9-5 CST):toll free 1-888-868-5501local 1-830-868-5500
Email: jerky@moment.net
V. Changes to our privacy policy.
Any changes or updates to Whittington’s Jerky, Inc. website privacy policies will be posted to this location.
Copyright 2001 - 2020. All Rights Reserved. WHITTINGTON’S JERKY, INC.
Design by custom Bigcommerce designerCart Designers - Experts in ecommerce webdesign.
